列車上的女孩
我丈夫曾跟我說過，我的想像力過於活躍
My husband used to tell me I have an overactive imagination.
我情不自禁
I can't help it.
比如說，你有沒有坐在火車上
I mean, haven't you ever been on a train
對住在軌道兩旁的人們的生活感到好奇？
and wondered about the lives of the people who live near the tracks?
那種你不可能經歷的生活
The lives you've never lived.
蕾切爾
這些就是我想知道的事
These are things I want to know.
一天兩次，我坐在前面第三節車廂
Twice a day I sit in the third car from the front
在那裏我可以清楚地看到我最喜歡的房子
where I have the perfect view into my favorite house:
貝克特路十五號…
Number 15 Beckett Road...
我不知道確切是那一天
I don't know when exactly.
我想大約在一年以前我開始注意到她
I suppose I started noticing her about a year ago
幾個月過去以後
and, gradually, as the months went past,
她漸漸變得對我重要起來…
she became important to me...
我不再是從前的那個女孩
I'm not the girl I used to be.
這個我想人們可以從我臉上看出來
I think people can see it on my face.
她就是我之所失
She's what I lost.
她就是我之所欲…
She's everything I want to be...
我想像她是個畫家…
I imagine she's a painter...
富有創造力；而他是醫生或建築師
She's creative. He's a doctor or an architect.
他笑聲爽朗
He has a good laugh.
她不會做飯
She can't cook.
我想知道每晚入睡前他們互相會說什麼話
I wonder what they say to each other before they go to sleep.
今天她的名字是傑絲，明天就可以是莉莎或安柏
Today her name is Jess, tomorrow it could be Lisa or Amber.
這全取決於當天的情況，取決於我的心情
It all depends on the day, it depends on my mood.
事實是：我不知道她的名字
The truth is, I don't know her name.
我不知道她是否是畫家，或他是否笑聲爽朗
I don't know if she paints or whether he has a good laugh.
我只知道他們知道愛…
I just know they know love...
有時我會出神地努力回憶…
Sometimes I catch myself trying to remember
…我最後一次與另一個人的真正意義上的接觸…
the last time I had meaningful contact with another person...
我曾經住在兩個門牌號之後——貝克特路十三號
I used to live two doors down... number 13 Beckett Road.
那是我的第一個家
It was my first home.
我們一起買的，那是我們的家
We bought it together. It was ours.
每天，我都告誡自己別去看
Every day, I tell myself not to look.
但我仍然會看…
But then I look...
- 你一個人嗎？ - 是的
- Are you alone?  - Yeah.
沒事，來吧，隨便坐
No, come. It's all yours.
- 你的寶貝好可愛，嗨，寶貝  - 謝謝
- Your baby's so cute. Hi, baby.  - Thank you.
- 他是…他是男孩？ - 是的
- Is it... Is it a boy?  - Yeah.
太可愛了，他…他多大了？
So sweet. How... how old is he?
- 六個月  - 六個月
- Six months.  - Six months.
好可愛啊
So sweet.
梅根
有位老師曾對我說，我是自我重塑的情婦
A teacher once told me I was a mistress of self-reinvention...
當時我不太確定這話是什麼意思
I wasn't really sure what it meant at the time.
但自從搬到這裏，我開始慢慢理解了…
But since moving here I've come to understand it...
六個月以前
哈德遜河畔阿茲利的生活平淡又無聊
Ardsley-on-Hudson is boring and routine.
這裏簡直就是個嬰兒工廠
It's a fucking baby factory.
我想重新開啟我的生活
I want to start my life over again.
到目前為止，我當過叛逆青少年
So far, I've been: rebellious teenager,
情侶
lover,
女侍者
waitress...
畫廊主管
gallery director,
保姆
nanny,
還有賤貨
and a whore.
不一定是按照這個次序
And not necessarily in that order.
我再也成為不了好妻子
I can't just be a wife anymore.
這就是為什麼我會徹夜不眠，盯著天花板
That's why I stay awake at night, staring at the ceiling.
事實上只有在我跑步時，我才覺得是我自己
In fact, the only time I feel like myself is when I'm running.
你一直有這樣的感覺嗎？
You always felt that way?
也許從大概十七歲起
Maybe since I was about seventeen.
和麥克在一起時
With Mac.
麥克？麥克是誰？
Mac? Who's Mac?
我哥哥最好的朋友
My brother's best friend.
那時我哥哥剛死…
My brother who died...
緊張時我容易微笑
I tend to smile when I'm nervous.
有時我會發笑
Sometimes, I laugh.
有一年時間，麥克和我住在一間狩獵小木屋裏
For a year, Mac and I lived in this hunting cabin.
我們瘋狂做愛
We started fucking.
我們是世界上最傷心的人
We were the saddest people we knew.
但從某種意義上說，那個木屋使我們幸福
But in a way, that cabin made us happy.
沒人能夠找到我們
No one could find us.
每個人都以為我們死了
Everyone thought we were dead.
假設今天你想逃跑，就在現在，你會去哪裏？
And if you were to run away today, right now, where would you go?
我曾讀到過如果被火車撞到，你的衣服會被火車撕掉
I read once that when a train hits, it can rip the clothes right off of you.
我非常確定斯科特認為保姆工作能使我不那麼焦躁
I'm pretty sure Scott thinks the nanny job is gonna make me less restless,
能使我想要懷孕…
make me wanna get pregnant...
但情況並非如此？
And that's not the case?
每天晚上做完工，我都跑著回家
When I finish work, every night I run home,
我站在淋浴下盡快洗掉我身上的嬰兒味道
and I get in the shower and wash the smell of that baby off me as fast as I can.
安娜
今天
今天早晨你醒來時，我過去把你抱過來和我躺在一起
When you woke up this morning I went and I brought you back to bed with me.
在我給你餵奶時，我們聽見爹地在廚房唱歌，是不是？
And when I was feeding you, we heard daddy singing from the kitchen, didn't we?
「祝你生日快樂，祝你生日快樂
Happy Birthday to you, Happy Birthday to you,
「祝你生日快樂，親愛的安娜，祝你生日快樂！」
Happy Birthday dear Anna, Happy Birthday to you!
爹地走上樓，端來一頓豐盛的早餐
Daddy came upstairs with a beautiful breakfast
那是他給媽咪做的，是嗎？
that he made for Mommy, didn't he?
是的，沒錯
Yes he did.
謝謝，梅根
Thank you, Megan.
好了
There you go.
噢，你好啊
Oh, hello.
我發誓，有的時候我感覺我的心都快要爆炸了
I swear I sometimes feel like my heart is gonna explode.
我是說，看看她
I mean, look at her.
看看她！
Look at her!
你不睡覺！
You're not sleeping!
- 喂？ - 你不睡覺…
- Hello?  - You're not sleeping...
喂？
Hello?
你好？
又給掛掉了？
Is that another hang-up?
抓著兩個角
And grab the corners.
- 抖一下  - 我另找了份工作
- And straighten.  - I got another job.
你什麼？
You what?
真的很抱歉，安娜
I'm really sorry, Anna.
我還以為你在這兒很快樂，我是說，看上去在這兒很快樂
I thought you were happy here. I mean, you seemed happy here...
我是的
I am.
只是這不是我想做的
It's just this isn't what I do.
照看孩子？
Take care of children?
或洗東西
Or laundry.
另一家畫廊看中了我
Another gallery head-hunted me.
- 很不錯  - 問題是，明天就開始
- That's great.  - The thing is, it starts tomorrow.
我明天要外出一整天，這樣真的很不著調
I'm out all day tomorrow. That is so uncool.
我真的不想這樣離開，孩子沒人看，但是你又不工作
I hate to leave you like this, without childcare, but, you don't have a job.
好吧，這樣說不太對
Ok, that sounded wrong.
- 我知道你忙於志願工作  - 不是志願工作
- I know that you're busy volunteering.  - It's not the volunteering.
而是買各種東西，是在農貿市場花幾個小時
It's all the shopping, it's spending hours in the farmer's market,
給她挑最合適的食物，是給紅薯削皮
it's finding the right foods for her, it's pureeing sweet potatoes.
我一邊做所有這些事情，一邊還要給她餵奶
And I do all of this at the same time as I'm nursing.
也許你也應該再回去工作
Maybe you should go back to work, too.
母親需要工作
Mothers need to work,
- 這樣其實對孩子也好  - 你怎麼知道？
- it's actually better for the kid.  - How would you know?
還你鑰匙
Your key.
沒有任何工作比撫養孩子更加重要！
There is no job more important than raising a child...
梅根，求你了…
Megan, please...
蕾切爾？你在幹嘛？
Rachel? What are you doing?
把寶貝還我
Give me my baby.
蕾切爾，你想要幹嘛？
Rachel, what are you doing?!
喂？
Hello?
謝謝
Thank you.
太美了
Beautiful.
今天她給你發了幾條短信？
How many times has she texted you today?
- 我不知道  - 她打到家裏三次
- I don't know.  - She called the landline three times.
- 你必須跟她談談  - 我知道
- You have to talk to her.  - I know.
- 這越來越瘋狂了  - 我會的，我知道，我知道
- It's getting crazy.  - I will. I know I know I know.
好吧
Okay.
一定會沒事的
It's going to be fine.
不總是沒事的嗎？
Isn't it always fine?
我不是把一切都弄得妥妥帖帖的嗎？
Don't I always make everything fine?
管它那麼多呢？今天是你的生日
Who gives a shit? It's your birthday.
你確定今晚不想讓我帶你出去？
You sure you don't want me to take you out tonight?
- 不用，我喜歡在家裏慶祝  - 打電話給梅根，讓她回來
- No, I like it at home.  - Call Megan. Ask her to come back.
她剛剛辭職了
She just quit.
- 她什麼？ - 她剛告訴我她找到了另一份工作
- She what?  - She just told me she got another job.
可惜，我以為你們兩個還挺合得來的呢
Shame. I thought you guys were kind of a good team together.
我也這麼以為
So did I.
蕾切爾 · 沃森
湯姆 · 沃森
蕾切爾
嘿，我是湯姆，抱歉沒聽到你電話
Hey, it's Tom. Sorry I missed you.
嘿，湯姆，是我，我只是想祝媽媽生日快樂
Hey, Tom, it's me. I just wanted to wish Momma happy birthday.
- 生日快樂，孩子他媽  - 蕾切爾！
- Happy birthday, Momma.  - Rachel!
天哪…
Jesus...
不，不，不！別，不要，凱茜，請住手！
No no no. No, don't, Cathy. Please stop it!
- 放鬆，放鬆  - 凱茜，別這樣！
- Relax. Relax.  - Cathy, come on!
我只需要喝點助我睡眠，我只需要喝一點點幫助我睡眠
I just need something to go to sleep. I just need a little bit to go to sleep.
這又是因為什麼？
What brought this on?
他又發了一張孩子的照片
He posted another picture of the baby.
- 非常可愛的照片  - 是嗎？
- It was a cute picture.  - Yeah?
臉書和醉醺醺的前妻成不了好朋友
Facebook and drunk ex-wives do not make good friends.
- 我自己來，我自己來  - 行了，我送你進自己房間
- I got it. I got it.  - Alright. I'll just get you to your room.
蕾切爾，你必須停止給他們打電話，明白嗎？
Rachel, you have to stop calling them. Okay?
我真的非常感激這個房間，真的
I really appreciate this room. I do.
我還以為我只會在這裏呆上一兩星期或一個月
I thought that I would just be here for a couple of weeks or a month.
是啊，那都已經兩年以前了
Yeah. That was two years ago.
睡點覺吧
Get some sleep.
試管受精很少第一次就成功的
IVF rarely works the first time.
你們想商量一下嗎？
Would you like a moment?
沒事的，親愛的，我們再做一次
It's okay, sweetie. We're gonna try again.
我們沒錢再做一次了
We can't afford to do it again.
等有錢了，我們再做
When we can, we will.
我想知道她在看什麼…
I wonder what she's looking at...
或者她是否根本沒看到這火車
Or if she even sees this train at all.
那個男人是誰？
Who is that man?
她這是想幹嘛？
What is she doing?
她是在拋棄掉這一切啊
She's throwing it all away.
應該是沒這個牌子的
「斯坦因霍爾茲伏特加」
安娜，昨夜我想著你就進入了夢鄉
Anna, I fell asleep last night thinking of you.
在夢裏我親吻著你的大腿內側，抓著你的胸脯
I dreamed about kissing the inside of your thighs. Holding your breasts.
天哪，我多希望現在我就在干你
God, I wish I was fucking you right now.
安娜，我愛你，我是那麼地愛你
Anna, I love you. I love you so much.
當這事落在我頭上時，我發現了幾十封電子郵件
When it happened to me, I found dozens of emails.
湯姆向她告白，他以前從沒有這樣的感覺
Tom told her that he'd never felt like this before.
他說用不了多久他們倆就可以在一起
He said it wouldn't be that much longer until they were together.
我知道人們會說：你不應該查他的電郵
I know what they say: You shouldn't check his email.
我太蠢了
I was stupid.
可我看到的信是地產商發來的
But when I saw it was from the realtor
我以為那只是垃圾郵件
I thought that it was just spam.
然後我意識到那些「X」真正代表的是他們的吻
And then I realized that they were kisses not Xs
由亞瑟 · 巴特利特於1971年創立的跨國不動產企業
而我丈夫操上了一個「二十一世紀」的房地產經紀人
and my husband was fucking a Century 21 Agent.
- 真狗血  - 的確狗血
- That sucks.  - It does.
她的名字叫安娜 · 博伊德，他說他愛上她了
Her name was Anna Boyd and he was in love with her.
過來一下
Come here for one second.
說「操你媽，安娜 · 博伊德」
Say "fuck you, Anna Boyd",
- 但要喊著說  - 好的
- but just yell it.  - Right.
操你媽，安娜 · 博伊德！
Fuck you, Anna Boyd!
那個賤貨現在住在我的房子裏
That bitch is living in my house.
那房子裏的東西都是我挑的，每一件都是我選的
I picked everything in that house. I picked everything.
我選的吃飯桌、廚房桌
I picked the dining table, the kitchen table.
我很好奇她是否知道…
I wonder if she knows that
就在她寶貝用餐的桌子上，我幹過湯姆
I fucked Tom on the same table that her baby eats at.
我真想告訴她
I just want to tell her.
我希望我能告訴她，我挑選了那房子裏的一切
I wish I could tell her. I picked everything in that house.
我他媽的挑選了那房子裏的一切！
I fucking picked everything in that house!
我一直找不到適當的措辭來描述我讀到那封…
I could never find the words to describe how I felt
…電郵時的感受
when I read that e-mail,
但今天早上，我找到了
but this morning, I did.
真的找到了
I did.
當我看到那個女人在親吻另一個人時…
When I saw that woman kissing someone else...
我…她背叛了她的丈夫，我感到…
I... Betraying her husband, I felt...
我感覺到了，我感覺到徹底的憤怒
I felt it. I felt pure rage.
好像是我的什麼東西又被人奪走了
Like something has been taken from me again.
如果有可能…如何有可能，我會徑直去她的家
If I could... If I could, I'd just go to her house.
我會走進廚房，找到正坐在桌旁的她
And I'd go in and find her sitting at the kitchen table.
我會用手攥住她長長的金髮，猛地拽向腦後
I'd wrap my hand in her long blonde hair and jerk her head back.
猛地向後一拽！
Just jerk it back!
然後我會把她拖倒在地
And then I'd pull her down to the ground
把她的頭一遍又一遍地砸向地面！
and I would just smash her head all over the floor!
閃開！別擋我道！閃開！
Move! Get out of my way! Move!
你個賤貨！
You whore!
天哪，蕾切爾！你這人他媽的怎麼回事？
Jesus Christ, Rachel! What the hell is wrong with you?
我花了一個小時開著車一直在找你！
I've spent the past hour driving around looking for you!
你他媽的把安娜嚇個半死，你知道嗎？
You scared the shit out of Anna, do you know that?
她以為你想要…她都想打電話報警了
She thought you were going to... She wanted to call the police.
所以…
So just...
別來打攪我們！
Leave us alone!
你盡可以毀掉你自己的生活，但絕不允許你破壞我們的
You can ruin your own life if you want to, but you're not gonna destroy ours.
我不會再保護你了
I'm not gonna protect you any more.
噢，我的天哪…
Oh my god...
蕾切爾，把門開開
Rachel, open the door.
- 凱茜，我現在需要點時間  - 你沒事吧？蕾切爾，快開門
- Cathy, I just need a sec.  - Are you ok? Rachel, open the door.
我得了病毒性腸胃炎
I have a stomach flu, okay?
你沒得腸胃炎，這他媽怎麼回事，蕾切爾？
You don't have a flu. What the fuck, Rachel?
我不是傻…
I'm not stupid...
- 蕾切爾！ - 凱茜，你走吧！
- Rachel!  - Cathy, just go away!
過來一下，就一下
Come here for one second.
- 說「操你媽，安娜 · 博伊德」  - 操你媽，安娜 · 博伊德！
- Say "fuck you, Anna Boyd."  - Fuck you, Anna Boyd!
你個賤貨！
You whore!
有誰想分享一下自己的戒酒天數嗎？三個月內的？
Anyone counting days one to ninety who would like to share a day count?
嘿，我叫詹森，我是個酒鬼
Hey, I'm Jason, I'm an alcoholic.
- 歡迎，詹森  - 我已經二十二天沒碰了
- Welcome, Jason.  - I've got twenty-two days back.
還有嗎？
Anyone else?
- 嗨，我叫蕾切爾…  - 歡迎，蕾切爾
- Hi, I'm Rachel, and...  - Welcome, Rachel.
今天是第一天，我想
This is day one, I suppose.
我來這裏是因為我…
I'm here because I...
因為我…
Because I...
因為我醒來時渾身是血
Because I woke up covered in blood.
我的胳膊滿是瘀傷…
And I had bruises all over my arm and...
通常這是由於我摔跤導致的，還經常有人扶我起來
It's usually from when I've fallen and someone has helped me up.
我丈夫…
My husband...
他常常告訴我前一天晚上我的行為
He used to tell me what I'd done the night before.
我知道像那樣子醒過來，你只會說你很抱歉
And I learned that when you wake up like that, you just say you're sorry.
你只會為你的所作所為而道歉
You just say you're sorry for what you did
為你成為這樣的人而道歉，並保證再也不會這麼做
and you're sorry for who you are and you're never gonna do it again.
但是你會的，還是會這麼做
But you do. You do it again.
有些時間…不見了
And there's... time missing.
我需要回憶
I need to remember.
好的，謝謝你，蕾切爾
Okay. Thank you, Rachel.
那跟無家可歸者有關，我不記得叫什麼名字了
It was that homeless thing. I don't remember what it was called.
- 對了，「安全庇護所」…  - 是的
- Oh, Safe Shelter...  - Yeah.
- 那是件筒式抹胸，對嗎？ - 是的，沒錯
- That was a tube top, right?  - Yeah, it was.
- 你喜歡吃惡魔的蛋嗎，瑪莎？ - 惡魔蛋？是的，喜歡
- Do you like Devil's Eggs, Martha?  - Deviled Eggs? Yeah, I do.
一種抹了芥末等調料的煮蛋
惡魔蛋
Deviled Eggs.
經典款
The classics.
有誰想嘗一個嗎？
Do you want to try one, anybody?
這個放到外面去，我不想把蛋和甜點放在一起
Those go outside. I don't want the eggs with the dessert.
放哪兒都他媽一樣，行嗎？你想把它們放這兒？
It doesn't fucking matter where they go, okay? So do you want to put them here?
你想把它們和你的熱狗放一起？還是想拿幾個和你的奎奴亞藜放一起？
Do you want them with your hot dogs? Or you can put a couple with your quinoa if you want.
或者你想把它們和你的色拉和玉米放一起，還放兩個到牆上！
Or do you want to put them with your other salad and your corn, and a couple on the wall!
- 蕾切爾！ - 我沒事，湯姆，住手！
- Rachel!  - I'm fine, Tom. Stop it!
你不支持我，你從沒支持過我
You didn't back me up. You never have my back.
- 你從沒支持過我  - 那是我老闆的老婆
- You never have my back.  - That's my boss's wife.
- 你那樣很可能會讓我丟飯碗的  - 我才他媽不管呢，我是你老婆
- You probably got me fired back there.  - I don't give a fuck. I'm your wife.
- 我是你老婆你卻從不…  - 蕾切爾！
- I'm your wife and you never...  - Rachel!
你卻從不他媽的支持我！
You never fucking support me!
求你別鬧了！嘿，別這樣，我需要你現在醒一醒
Please stop. Hey, come on. I need you to focus here.
- 別他媽的那樣對我說話！ - 放鬆！
- Don't fucking talk to me like that!  - Relax!
- 蕾切爾，你回來了  - 凱茜，對不起了
- Rachel, there you are.  - Cathy, I'm sorry.
我需要把我東西規整一下，我…
I need to get my shit together. I'm...
你一定是沃森小姐，我是萊利警探
You must be Miss Watson. I'm Detective Riley.
這位是加斯基爾警探，我們需要問你幾個問題
This is Detective Gaskill. We need to ask you a few questions.
- 和什麼有關？ - 能坐下麼？
- What's this about?  - Want to sit down?
你能告訴我星期五晚上你在哪裏？
Can you tell me where you were Friday night?
我…我先在城裏工作，然後…
I was at work in the city. And then...
- 然後我去看望我丈夫了  - 你的意思是你前夫？
- And then I went to visit my husband.  - You mean your EX-husband?
是的，所以我在哈德遜河畔阿茲利下了火車，然後…
Yes. So I got off the train at Ardsley-on-Hudson. And then...
然後我覺得這是個壞主意
And then I decided that it was a bad idea.
大概是什麼時候你得到這樣的結論的？
Around what time did you reach that conclusion?
我回到這裏是十一點鐘
I was back here by 11:00.
是的，是的
Yeah. Yeah.
你回這裏的路上，有沒有在任何地方逗留？
On your way back here, did you stop anywhere?
沒有
No.
你幾點在那兒坐的火車？
And what time did you take the train there?
- 呃，六點  - 那麼…那幾個小時…
- Um, 6:00.  - So... What did you do
…你在阿茲利幹什麼呢，如果你沒去看你的前夫？
during those hours in Ardsley if you weren't seeing your ex-husband?
記不記得見過這個女人？
Do you remember seeing this woman?
她為你前夫工作
She worked for your ex-husband.
- 她失蹤了  - 你什麼意思，她失蹤了？
- She's gone missing.  - What do you mean she's missing?
她丈夫說她再也沒有回家，就是在你在…
Her husband said she never came back home the same night
…哈德遜河畔阿茲利下火車的同一天晚上
you got off the train in Ardsley-on-Hudson.
- 我只是…我…  - 你認識梅根 · 希普韋爾嗎？
- I was just...I was...  - Do you know Megan Hipwell?
- 不  - 你見過她嗎？
- No.  - Did you see her?
- 沒有，我想我沒見過  - 是因為你處於醉酒狀態？
- No. I don't think so.  - Is that because you were inebriated?
只是想澄清一下，你說你星期五去工作了？
Just to clarify, you said you were at work Friday?
你是指你在公共關係部的那份工作嗎？
Are you referring to your job in Public Relations?
是的
Right.
可是據我瞭解，一年多前你就從那兒被解雇了
It's my understanding you were fired from that job over a year ago
因為你的酗酒問題？
because of your drinking problem?
好吧，今天就到這兒吧
Ok. That's enough for now.
如果你想起些什麼了，給我們打電話
If you're able to remember anything else, give us a call.
你真的被解雇了嗎？
Did you really get fired?
你看，我是不想讓你擔心我付不起房租…
Look, I didn't want you to worry that I couldn't pay the rent...
既然你沒了工作，那你整天都在幹什麼？
If you don't have a job, then what do you do everyday?
我…
I...
- 我…我坐火車  - 你什麼？
- I ride the train.  - You what?
我坐火車上紐約再坐回來
I ride the train to New York and back.
你的贍養費都用在這上面了？買哪兒都不去的車票？
That's what your alimony's paying for? Tickets to nowhere?
- 這真他媽的怪異，蕾切爾！ - 行了，行了
- That's really fucking weird, Rachel!  - Okay. Okay.
我…我上了火車
I got on the train.
然後，我…我下了火車，我不知道！一切都太模糊了…
And then, I got off the train. I don't know! It's very unclear...
你什麼都不記得了，是嗎？
You don't remember anything, do you?
你知道，我讀到過在長島有個男的，他糊塗了
You know, I read about this man in Long Island who blacked out.
他離開酒吧，開車回到…
He left a bar and drove to the house
…他從小長大的房子，把裏面的住戶一個個扎死
that he'd grown up in, stabbed its occupants to death.
他第二天早上醒來，對所做的事全然不知
He woke up the next morning oblivious to what he did
直到警察來把他抓走…
until the police came to get him.
- 蕾切爾！ - 什麼？什麼？
- Rachel!  - What? What?
你必須搬走，我不能再這樣做了
You have to leave. I can't do this anymore.
- 我會給你幾周時間  - 等一下
- I'll give you a few weeks.  - Hold on.
等一下
Hold on.
- 萊利警探！萊利警探！ - 是的，我同意你說的，可是…
- Detective Riley! Detective Riley!  - Yeah, I agree with you, but...
我見到有人和梅根 · 希普韋爾在一起，不過不是在週五晚上
I saw someone with Megan Hipwell, but not on Friday night.
她…她有了婚外情，她有一個情人
She was having an affair. She had a lover.
- 我就是想告訴你這個  - 我還以為你不認識她呢
- That's what I'm trying to tell you.  - I thought you didn't know her.
- 是的，但是我看見她了  - 你在哪兒看見的？
- No. But I saw her.  - You saw her where?
我…我從火車上看見她，她站在平台上，和那個男人
I saw her from the train. She was standing on the deck with this man.
- 和他丈夫，斯科特 · 希普韋爾？ - 不是，那不是她丈夫
- With her husband, Scott Hipwell?  - No. It wasn't him.
那個男人不一樣，他們吻在了一起
This man was different. And they were kissing.
哇哦，這相當地巧啊，不是麼？
Wow. That's pretty coincidental, isn't it?
你碰巧在一列火車上，它在一個你不認識但不知怎麼…
You just happen to be on a train at the same exact moment that a woman you don't know,
…又能認出的女人正在出軌的那一刻恰好經過？
but somehow recognize, is cheating on her husband?
- 我知道這聽起來很荒唐，可…  - 鄰居們星期五晚上…
- I know it sounds crazy, but...  - Neighbors saw a drunk woman
…在她家附近見到過一個醉醺醺的女人
in the vicinity of her house Friday night.
梅根 · 希普韋爾的確和安娜 · 沃森有點像
Megan Hipwell does bear a resemblance to Anna Watson.
沃森太太報告說有時你會未獲邀請地去他們家
Mrs. Watson reported that you go to their house sometimes uninvited.
甚至有一次，你闖進去抱走了他們的孩子
And that on one occasion, you actually broke in and took their child.
我給你來點忠告吧
Let me give you some advice.
別再回貝克特路，別再聯繫你的前夫
Don't go back to Beckett Road. Don't contact your ex-husband.
別再去任何跟安娜 · 沃森或她的寶貝很近的地方
Don't go anywhere near Anna Watson or her baby.
- 你在聽我說嗎？ - 是的
- Are you listening to me?  - Yes.
你已經不再在那裏生活了
You don't live there anymore.
離遠點
Stay away.
你知道，我總是撒謊
You know, I lie all the time.
四個月以前
我對斯科特撒謊，我對你撒謊
I lie to Scott. I lie to you.
我知道這不是心理治療的關注點，但是…
I mean I know that's not the point of therapy, but...
我必須保持事物的模糊性
I have to keep things vague.
把所有男人都混起來，所有的前任、情人
Jumble up all the men, the Exes, the lovers.
不管他們是誰，不管他們給我怎樣的感覺
It doesn't matter who they are. It matters how they make me feel.
撒謊就像是做一次旅行
Lying is like taking a trip.
就像是有了一個秘密
It's like having a secret.
就像是觸摸你自己而沒有任何人知道…
It's like touching yourself and no one else knows...
除了你自己
Except you.
但是你只是在假裝
But you're just pretending.
你只是在假裝觸摸你自己
You're just pretending to touch yourself.
斯科特佔有慾很強，容易妒忌
Scott's possessive. Jealous.
他喜歡擁有我
He likes to own me.
他破解了我所有的密碼
He figures out all my passwords.
這倒是有點性感
Which is kinda sexy.
所以當我昨晚回家時，斯科特正在我筆記本電腦上好奇地…
So, when I came home last night, Scott was on my laptop wondering why...
斯科特的行為是不正常的
Scott's behavior is not normal.
這是感情虐待的一種形式
It's a form of emotional abuse.
你害怕過斯科特嗎？
Are you ever afraid of Scott?
這不是虐待
It's not abuse.
不在乎的話就不是虐待，我不在乎
Not if you don't care. And I don't.
也許對你來說，這變成了一種正常態
Maybe it's become a normal state for you.
我總是在想著你，這正常嗎？
Is it normal I think about you all the time?
幾乎正好一周以前
Almost exactly a week ago,
梅根 · 希普韋爾走出貝克特路十五號後就消失了
Megan Hipwell walked out of Number 15 Beckett Road and disappeared.
再也沒人看見過她，她的電話和銀行卡週五以後…
No one has seen her since. Neither her phone nor her bank cards
…也再沒有使用過
have been used since Friday.
阿茲利女子仍沒找到
一個很棒的女人，雖然個性內斂卻有顆溫暖的心
A wonderful woman. An intensely private person with a warm heart.
在她十六歲時，她失去了哥哥
She lost a brother when she was sixteen,
她的父母也在幾年前雙雙過世
and both her parents died a few years ago.
斯科特 · 希普韋爾盼望出現任何能提供她消息的人
Scott Hipwell urges anyone with information to please come forward.
- 你是梅根的朋友？ - 是的，我叫蕾切爾
- You're Megan's friend?  - Yes. Rachel.
進來吧
Come in.
- 想來杯咖啡嗎？ - 好的，謝謝
- Do you want a coffee?  - Sure. Thank you.
不好意思，亂的很
Sorry it's a mess.
我在找她的身份證和出生證
I've been hunting for her social, birth certificate.
警察什麼都需要
The cops need a lot.
- 我們以前見過面嗎？ - 我…我想沒見過
- Have we met somewhere before?  - I don't think so.
- 那你怎麼認識梅根的？ - 呃…通過畫廊
- And you know Megan from?  - From the gallery.
- 你是藝術家？ - 唔，我想算是吧
- Are you an artist?  - Well, I like to think so.
你在電話裏說你想告訴我有關梅根的一些事
So you said on the phone, you wanted to tell me something about Megan.
你想告訴我什麼？
What did you want to tell me?
星期五上午，我看見你妻子和一個人在一起
I saw your wife with someone, on Friday morning.
和誰？
With who?
她站在你們的平台上面
She was up there on your porch.
我是從火車上看見的，因為每天我都坐車去曼哈頓
I saw her from the train because I commute to Manhattan everyday
我正好經過這裏
and I go straight past here.
她吻了他
She kissed him.
他們在親吻
They were kissing.
我很抱歉，我知道聽到這樣的事真的很可怕
I'm sorry. I know this is a terrible thing to hear.
我知道這是什麼感覺
I know how it feels.
他長什麼樣？
What did he look like?
他…他有平均的身高
He was average height.
他是黑色頭髮
He had dark hair.
他們在外面的平台上？
And they were out there on the porch?
是的
Yes.
操！
Fuck.
噢，不，不，不，謝謝
No, no, no. Thank you.
好吧，當然
OK. Sure.
可能吧，我不知道，也許這樣反而倒好？
It could, I don't know. Maybe it's a good thing?
這樣可能意味著她沒事
It could mean she's all right.
- 她只是跟著別人跑了  - 是的
- She just ran off with someone.  - Right.
- 她跟你談過嗎？ - 噢，不，我沒聽到過任何事
- She talked to you?  - Oh no. I haven't heard anything.
你跟她足夠熟悉，都知道我們住的地方
You know her well enough to know where we live.
梅根沒有太多朋友
Megan doesn't have many friends.
唔，我曾在附近居住過…她和我，我們學過瑜伽…
Well, I used to live nearby... She and I, we took yoga...
我們一起學過普拉提課
We took pilates together.
我想我該走了，我覺得我已經佔用你太多時間了
I think I should go, I feel like I've taken up too much of your time.
非常抱歉要以這樣的方式告訴你這事
So sorry to have had to tell you that in that way.
你覺得你能認出他來嗎？如果你見到他？
Do you think you'd recognize him again? If you saw him?
我不知道
I don't know.
有個傢伙，心理醫生
There was a guy, a therapist.
他的名字叫阿布迪克…阿布迪克
His name's Abdic. Abdic.
卡馬爾 · 阿布迪克
Kamal Abdic.
你看到的是他嗎？
Is that who you saw?
我不知道，真的說不好
I don't know. I really can't tell.
她他媽的花很多時間和她心理醫生在一起
She spends a lot of fucking time with her shrink.
我想起來了，就…就是他
I remember... That's him.
我想起來了，就是他
I remember. That's him.
對不起
I'm sorry.
你在哪兒？你在哪兒？
Where are you? Where are you?
兩個月以前
你在哪兒？
Where are you?
離我遠點！
Stay away from me.
這太愚蠢了，每一次談話他都會扯到要我懷孕
This is so stupid. He makes every conversation about getting pregnant.
- 每次我們去那裏…  - 去哪裏？
- And every time we go there...  - Where?
談到那個話題
To that subject.
什麼話題？
What subject?
梅根
Megan.
什麼話題？
What subject?
沒事的
It's okay.
梅根
Megan.
沒事的，梅根
All right, Megan.
我們不應該…
We shouldn't...
不
No.
梅根
Megan.
別讓事情一發不可收拾，我們再也不能合作
Don't make it impossible for us to work together.
梅根，我可能會被吊銷執照的
Megan, I could lose my practice.
我才他媽不管！我才他媽不管你的什麼狗屁執照！
I don't give a fuck. I don't give a fuck about your fucking practice!
我才他媽不管…
I don't give a fuck...
卡馬爾 · 阿布迪克醫生被帶走詢問有關哈德遜河畔阿茲利…
Dr. Kamal Abdic has been brought in for questioning on the disappearance
…居民梅根 · 希普韋爾的失蹤一事
of Ardsley-on-Hudson resident, Megan Hipwell.
根據消息來源，他是希普韋爾太太的心理醫生…
He was, according to sources, Mrs. Hipwell's psychiatrist...
幾年以來，我第一次有了目標
For the first time in ages I have purpose.
或至少我有了分心的事…
Or at least, I have a distraction...
我希望梅根會平安無事地現身，真的
I want Megan to show up safe and sound. I do.
斯科特：我們需要盡快見面
SCOTT: We need to meet ASAP
只是現在還不到時候
Just not quite yet.
嗨
Hi.
- 怎麼了？ - 阿布迪克被放出來了
- What's wrong?  - Abdic's been released.
什麼？！
What?!
沒有足夠的證據
There wasn't enough evidence.
因為是我讓他被抓起來的，他開口了，談了很多
And because I'm the one that got him arrested, he talked. A lot.
他們…他們會對他立案的，只是需要些時間
They'll build a case against him, it'll just take some time.
你十分確定他就是你看見的和梅根在一起的那個傢伙？
Are you totally sure he's the guy you saw Megan with?
是的
Yes.
- 你最好他媽的確定  - 我不明白…
- You sure as fuck better be.  - I don't understand.
- 警察認為是我幹的  - 是啊，可是他是那個…
- The police think I did it.  - Yeah, but he's the one...
他告訴他們梅根很不幸，我是個妒忌心強喜歡控制的丈夫
He told them Megan's miserable, that I'm a jealous, controlling husband.
我相信他們只是想把你的嫌疑排除…
I'm sure that they're just trying to rule you out...
阿布迪克告訴他們我打她
Abdic told them I'm abusive.
在她出走的時候，我…我也不去追她
When she walked out, I didn't go after her.
說我從不打電話看看她如何了
I never called to check on her.
說我去他媽的運動酒吧，喝得酩酊大醉
I went to a sports bar, for fuck's sake, and got drunk.
不，我們只需要找到更多的阿布迪克的證據
No. We just need to find more evidence on Abdic.
我已經花了一整天檢查她的東西
I've spent the whole day going through her stuff.
沒有電郵，什麼都沒有，沒有信件、電郵，一無所有
There's no emails, there's nothing, no letters, no emails. Nothing.
有那麼一瞬間，我都想親自聯繫阿布迪克了…
For a second, I thought about contacting Abdic myself...
媽的破電話響個不停！
Fucking phone won't stop!
我是斯科特，是…是，等一下，等一下
This is Scott. Yeah. Hold on. Hold on.
你不介意？
Do you mind?
你好沉啊，你好胖啊，你是個小胖紙
You're heavy. You're a fatty. You're a little fatty.
蕾切爾？不，安娜，進屋裏去
Rachel? No. Anna, get in the house.
你…你老婆星期五晚上打了我！
Your wife hit me on Friday night!
- 你在說什麼呢？ - 是的，她打了，是的，她打我了
- What are you talking about?  - Yes. Yes, she did. Yes, you did.
然後她…然後她上了你的車
And then she got in your car.
不，她說那天晚上你衝她叫喊
No. She said you yelled at her that night.
不，不是那麼回事！
No. That is not what happened!
她…她在隧道裏，她…她打了我
She was in the tunnel. And she hit me.
我不想當街和你爭吵，現在是大白天你已經醉了
I won't argue in the street. The middle of the day and you're drunk.
我沒醉，湯姆！
I'm not drunk, Tom!
我老婆害怕你
My wife is scared of you.
怕什麼？
Of what?
我不知道你是開玩笑還是什麼，我們就從綁架孩子說起
I don't even know if that's a joke or not. Let's start with child abduction.
那是胡說！你知道根本…不是那麼回事
That's bullshit. You know that's not... how it happened.
你我都很清楚你能幹出什麼事來
You and I both know what you're capable of.
你剛去斯科特 · 希普韋爾家了？
You were just at Scott Hipwell's house?
- 你為什麼去斯科特 · 希普韋爾家？ - 因為我想幫他…幫他
- Why are you at Scott Hipwell's house?!  - Because I'm helping him.
幫什麼？
How?
- 幫他找到梅根  - 你都不認識梅根！
- To try and find Megan.  - You don't even know Megan!
蕾切，我覺得你誰都幫不了
Rach. I don't think you're helping anybody.
那麼你來這裏是想恢復你失去的記憶
So you're here because you want to uncover lost memories.
- 是這樣嗎？ - 你有口音
- Is that correct?  - You have an accent.
什麼？
Pardon?
不好意思，我…我沒想到你會有口音
Sorry. I wasn't expecting you to have an accent.
是啊，你也有口音
Well, you have an accent.
- 你從哪兒來？ - 我是美國公民
- Where are you from?  - I'm an American citizen.
但是我想你不是來這裏談論我的
But I guess you're not here to talk about me.
- 除非你真的是…  - 不…不，對不起，我只是…
- Unless, you are...  - No. I'm sorry.
我只是想找個話題
I was just trying to make conversation.
暫時失憶，你經歷的是暫時性失憶
The blackouts. You're experiencing blackouts.
你想跟我聊聊你的情況嗎？
Do you want to tell me about them?
唔，我醒著的時候，當有人告訴我我做過的事時
Well, when I wake up, and when someone tells me what I've done,
感覺那根本不像我，我根本不會做出那樣的事
it just doesn't feel like me or like something that I would do.
我為此感覺很糟，但是…
I feel bad about it.
但是一切都似乎隔得那麼遙遠，彷彿我做了一個…
But it's like it's so far removed that I have a...
我感覺還不夠糟
I just don't feel bad enough.
你想為你的所作所為承擔起個人的責任
You want to take personal responsibility for what you've done,
但是你發現很難感到有責任，因為你甚至都不記得了
but you find it difficult to feel accountable because you can't even remember it.
是嗎？
Yeah?
- 是啊  - 那麼蕾切爾，除了喜歡喝酒…
- Yeah.  - So, Rachel, besides drinking...
顯然你喝酒的吧
Because you clearly drink.
你今天就喝了不少酒，有沒有？
You've been drinking today, haven't you?
你還喜歡別的什麼？有沒有任何業餘愛好？
What else do you enjoy? Do you have any hobbies?
我喜歡畫畫，藝術，我想
I like to draw. Art, I guess.
很好，我們可以試著通過畫畫來恢復你的部分記憶
Good. We can try to regain some of your memories by drawing them.
我試過了，不起作用
I've tried it. It doesn't work.
你有沒有一直往前追溯到你開始大量飲酒的時候？
Have you ever tracked all the way back to when you started drinking heavily?
那是什麼時候？
When was that?
當時我還和湯姆在一起，但是我懷不上孩子
It was with Tom. When I couldn't get pregnant.
誰是湯姆？
Who's Tom?
他是我的前夫
He's my ex-husband.
你想談談那些事嗎？
Do you want to talk about that?
我真的很想要個寶寶
I really wanted a baby.
我們想盡一切辦法但都不管用
We tried everything and nothing worked.
這絕對地…
And it just absolutely...
這令我心碎
It just broke my heart.
所以我傷心欲絕，然後…
So I got really sad and then...
酒精摧毀了我們
The booze just broke us.
對
Okay.
接著說
Tell me more.
我曾經注意到一對完美夫妻
I used to watch this perfect couple.
他們簡直就是真愛的化身
And they were just the embodiment of true love.
那好像是你一直希望得到的那種愛
It's like the kind of love you always want.
可是後來，她卻背叛了他
And then, she betrayed him.
這件事觸動了我內心的什麼…
And it's sparked something in me...
說實話你為什麼來這裏，蕾切爾？
Why are you really here, Rachel?
因為我害怕我自己
Because I'm afraid of myself.
七月五號：一點三十三、一點三十四、一點三十七…
July 5th: 1:33, 1:34, 1:37...
她在凌晨一點三十八又打過一次，然後在下午的一點四十四、一點四十五、兩點十五多次打來
She calls again 1:38 and then she calls again at 1:44, 1:45, 2:15 PM.
然後是七月六號…你知道我的意思
And then July 6th... You get the point.
有時她一天給他發來幾十條短信
She sometimes texted him dozens of times a day.
- 但這些都是匿名號碼發來的  - 匿名就是蕾切爾
- But these are all from an unknown number.  - Unknown is Rachel.
你只有撥號的紀錄
You have a log of the calls.
但是沒有他們互相通話的內容的紀錄
You don't have a log of what they're saying to each other.
你看，自從那次嬰兒事件之後，她有沒有再回過你們家？
Look, has she been back to the house since the incident with your child?
據我所知沒有
Not that I know.
這樣的話也許可以給你立一個二級騷擾的案子
Well, then you might have a case for harassment in the second degree,
但是這些都是短信，並不構成威脅，所以…
but these are texts, they're not threats, so...
她一直在斯科特 · 希普韋爾家周圍轉悠，非常頻繁
She's been hanging around Scott Hipwell's house. A lot.
我知道，現在存在非常多也許有意義的線索
I'm aware. There are a lot of loose ends here that suggest something,
但是都不能太說得通
but they don't add up to much.
如果你能給我提供些更加可靠的…
If you can bring me something more solid...
你還需要什麼？
What more do you need?
證據，確鑿證據
Evidence. Real evidence?
你確定你丈夫不想與他前妻保持聯繫嗎？
You sure your husband doesn't want to stay in touch with his ex-wife?
什麼？不，她在騷擾我們！
What? No. She's harassing us.
他也是這麼說的？
Is that what he calls it?
湯姆
伊維
密碼不對，再試一次
湯姆
安娜
密碼不對，再試一次
湯姆
蕾切爾
密碼不對，再試一次
嗨
Hi.
- 嗨  - 我院子裏都是記者
- Hi.  - Reporters are in my yard.
到處都是，我沒別的地方可去了
Everywhere. I didn't know where else to go.
進來吧
Come in.
警探剛…
The detective just...
警探剛告訴我長久以來我一直盼望聽到的消息
The detective just told me something I've wanted to hear for a long time.
她懷孕了
She's pregnant.
她告訴了她心理醫生而不是我
She told her shrink but not me.
我一直想要孩子
I wanted a family,
可她卻是步步與我作對
but she fought me every step of the way.
我們總是為此爭吵
We always fought about it.
梅根有沒有向你說起過我的什麼事？
Did Megan ever say anything about me to you?
她愛過你
She loved you.
她愛你的方式就是人們夢寐以求的相愛方式
She loved you in ways that people only dream of being loved.
一個月以前
你不該在這裏
You shouldn't be here.
我只想…
I just...
我需要告訴什麼人
I need to tell someone,
就一次
just once.
就是想大聲說出來
Just say it out loud.
我想告訴你
I want to tell you.
然後我就走，我發誓
And then I'll be gone, I swear.
那時我孕了
I got pregnant.
在我十七歲時
I was seventeen.
我自己生下了孩子
I had her by myself.
她長著黑色眼睛和金色頭髮
She had dark eyes and blond hair.
我以為這樣會很難，但實際並不難
I expected it to be hard, but it wasn't.
很容易
It was easy.
因為我愛她
Because I loved her.
我愛她
I loved her.
我叫她伊麗莎白
I called her Elizabeth.
麗比
Libby.
那是在十二月
It was December.
我們大吵了一架，我和麥克
We'd gotten in a fight, me and Mac.
他一走了之
He'd gone off and left.
屋頂正漏著雨
The roof was leaking.
我感到徹骨的寒冷，於是就躲進了浴缸
I was freezing cold, so I got in the tub.
我把麗比帶在身邊
I brought Libby in with me,
讓她依偎在我胸前
put her on my chest,
她的頭就在我的頦下
her head just under my chin.
我睡了過去
I fell asleep.
我鬆開了她
I let her go.
我不敢正視
I couldn't look.
我不想看到這一幕
I didn't want to see it.
我不想看到她
I didn't want to see her.
我把她用毯子包裹住
I wrapped her in a blanket.
然後掩埋了她
And I buried her.
後來…
Then...
有天晚上麥克出去了
Mac went out that night.
就再也沒有回來
And he never came back.
他再也沒有回來
He never came back.
我想念我們的家
I missed our home.
所以有一天在我喝醉後，我決定去那裏看看
So one day when I was drunk, I decided to go there.
前門是開著的，所以我並沒有闖進去
The front door was open. It's not like I broke in.
然後我聽見了伊維
And then I heard Evie.
伊維是誰？
Who's Evie?
湯姆的寶寶
Tom's baby.
我知道這聽上去很瘋狂
I know this sounds insane,
但是我只是想抱抱她
but I just wanted to hold her.
就抱一會兒
Just for a moment.
蕾切爾？你在幹嘛？！
Rachel? What are you doing?!
你想要幹嘛？
What are you doing?
蕾切爾…
Rachel...
我沒有想要傷害她
I wasn't going to hurt her.
我絕不可能傷害她
I would never hurt her.
我只是想抱抱她
I just wanted to hold her.
發現部分腐爛的屍體…發現女性屍體…
Partially decomposed body found... Female body found...
死因是強力鈍擊傷…發現部分腐爛的屍體…
Death a result of blunt force trauma. Partially decomposed body.
梅根 · 希普韋爾…目前變成了對殺人案的調查…
Megan Hipwell. Investigation now being called a homicide.
有消息說所發現的部分腐爛的屍體…
Sources say the partially decomposed body found
…是失蹤的阿茲利女子梅根 · 希普韋爾，死因是強力鈍擊傷
is missing Ardsley woman Megan Hipwell. Death a result of blunt force trauma.
梅根 · 希普韋爾的失蹤目前變成了對殺人案的調查
Megan Hipwell's investigation now being called a homicide.
希普韋爾先生？
Mr. Hipwell?
怎麼了？
What's wrong?
對不起
I'm sorry.
這讓我想起以前我看著你…
This reminds me of when I used to watch
…穿戴整齊，然後再回到她身邊的情景
you getting dressed before going back to her.
回到這所房子裏來
Back to this house.
我其實挺懷念當第三者時的感覺
I actually miss being the other woman.
- 欺騙蕾切爾有沒有讓你很享受？ - 這算什麼問題？
- Did you enjoy cheating on Rachel?  - Seriously?
我們能不能別受她擺佈？
Can we not fixate on her?!
- 我今天又看見她了  - 在哪兒？
- I saw her again today.  - Where?
今天下午當警察帶斯科特回家時，她就在街對面
This afternoon when the police brought Scott back home. She was across the street.
她看見我時變得具有攻擊性
And when she saw me she got aggressive.
怎麼個攻擊性？
Aggressive how?
要是蕾切爾殺了梅根呢？
What if Rachel killed Megan?
蕾切爾沒殺梅根
Rachel did not kill Megan.
那她為什麼偷偷摸摸地圍著斯科特家轉？
Then why is she creeping around Scott's house?
- 她很危險這你知道  - 安娜，親愛的
- She's dangerous and you know it.  - Anna, sweetheart,
蕾切爾很傷心
Rachel is a sad person.
她完全是無害的
She's completely harmless.
你在這裏幹嘛？你…你怎麼進來的？
What are you doing here? How did you get in?
過來
Come here.
和我共飲啤酒
Have a beer with me.
我…我現在不想喝
I'm not drinking right now.
萊利警探昨晚來看我
Detective Riley came to see me last night.
檢驗結果我不是父親
It turns out I'm not the father.
心理醫生也不是
Neither is the shrink.
我老婆有沒有向你袒露過還有第三個男人？
Did my wife confide in you about a third man?
坐下
Sit down.
坐下！
Sit down!
你看，我不知道…我不知道這是怎麼…
Look, I don't know what this is about...
噢，拜託！你和梅根不是要好朋友嗎？
Come on! You and Megan were such good friends.
你一定是知道的
You must have known.
- 承認吧  - 承認什麼？
- Admit it.  - Admit what?
承認你從沒他媽的遇見過我老婆！
Admit that you never even fucking met my wife!
警探說你甚至不認識梅根
The Detective said you didn't even know Megan.
她也用了些其他的詞
She used other words too.
酒癮，也許甚至精神不穩定？
Alcoholic. Maybe even mentally unstable?
對不起，我真的只是想幫你
I am sorry. I was honestly just trying to help.
你是湯姆的瘋子前妻！
You're Tom's crazy ex!
你他媽的打算何時告訴我這一點，哈？
When the fuck were you going to tell me that?
現在警探甚至問我是否你和我搞在一起了？！
And now the detective is asking if you and I are in a relationship?!
你？！打死我都不會喜歡像你這樣的人！
You?! I would never even get near someone like you!
我老婆死了，而你卻在對我撒謊！？
My wife is dead, and you're lying to me!?
你這人哪有毛病？誰會做這樣的事？
What's wrong with you? Who does this?
我必須告訴你梅根婚外情的事
I needed to tell you about Megan's affair,
要是你瞭解我湯姆前妻身份，你就不會相信我！
and you wouldn't have believed me if I was just Tom's ex!
那我要謝謝你了，你知道，為了讓阿布迪克指認我為嫌疑犯！
Well, thank you, you know. For getting Abdic to point the finger at me!
為了讓警察說你和我正幹得歡！
For getting the cops to say that you and I are fucking!
它們進展如何，嗯？
How are they going, huh?
我是說，那些療程？
You know? The sessions?
和醫生的？
With the doctor?
我想瞭解阿布迪克，我去找他是為了幫你
I wanted to know about Abdic and I went to him to help you.
你只是個可悲的沒有生活的騙子
You're just a sad liar with no life.
- 你滿嘴謊言！ - 求你了，別這樣！
- You're all liars.  - Please, don't!
我需要提交一份證言
I need to file a statement.
- 名字？ - 蕾切爾 · 沃森
- Name?  - Rachel Watson.
彼特？我來吧
Pete? I got this.
你想提交一份證言？我聽著呢
You wanted to file a statement? I'm listening.
斯科特 · 希普韋爾剛剛攻擊了我
Scott Hipwell just assaulted me.
你是說你的新男朋友斯科特 · 希普韋爾？
You mean your new boyfriend Scott Hipwell?
不，我們…我們只是朋友
No. We were just friends.
但這正是你所希望的，不是嗎？
But that's what you wanted, isn't it?
我是說，你讓他在你的公寓裏過夜，對嗎？
I mean, you got him to stay overnight at your apartment, right?
- 你…你需要瞭解來龍去脈  - 我知道來龍去脈
- You need the context.  - I know the context.
但是我想要確定的是你是何時開始對希普韋爾先生著迷的
But what I'm trying to determine is when your obsession with Mr. Hipwell began.
是在他懷孕的妻子被謀殺前還是謀殺後？
Was it before or after his pregnant wife was murdered?
我是說，你們過去曾經是鄰居？
I mean, you were neighbors at one point?
- 我認識他是在…  - 在我詢問你之後
- I met him after...  - After being questioned by me,
你去找了一個比自己看起來更像嫌疑犯的人做朋友
you befriend another even more obvious suspect than yourself,
然後你想辦法使他受到了牽連，與此同時還希望他會幹你
and then you manage to get him to incriminate himself all the while hoping he'll fuck you.
我來這裏想要幫助你
I came here trying to help you.
他剛剛攻擊了我在我自己家裏！
He just assaulted me in my own house!
那晚有人看見你在那塊區域
You were seen in the area that night.
有好幾個小時你說你記不起來了
There are several hours that you say you can't account for.
就是斯科特，斯科特 · 希普韋爾殺了他妻子
It was Scott. Scott Hipwell killed his wife.
不，他沒有
No. He didn't.
一家運動酒吧的監控錄像證實了希普韋爾先生整晚的下落
Surveillance footage from a sports bar accounts for Mr. Hipwell's whereabouts that night.
你在撒謊，你一直在撒謊
You're lying. You're lying.
告訴我發生什麼了
Tell me what happened.
沒事的
It's okay.
告訴我
Tell me.
我不知道…
I don't know...
梅根 · 希普韋爾是你殺的嗎？
Did you murder Megan Hipwell?
上星期五
LAST FRIDAY
嗨
Hi.
我需要見你
I need to see you.
能不能請你過來一下？
Can you please come over?
我仍然能看見她黑色的眼睛
I can still see her dark eyes.
我能聞到她的肌膚
I can smell her skin.
我能感覺到她有多冷
I can feel how cold she was.
原諒你自己
Forgive yourself.
你沒必要害怕會變得孤獨
You don't have to be afraid of being alone.
你不孤獨
You're not alone.
你會沒事的
You'll be fine.
你和你的寶貝會沒事的
You and your baby will be fine.
你為什麼跟著我？
Why are you following me?
你為什麼來這兒？
Why are you here?
我可以問你同樣的問題
I could ask you the same question.
我看見你了
I saw you.
那天晚上我在隧道裏看見過你，我看見你在那兒
I saw you that night in the tunnel. I saw you there.
- 我…我知道我看見你在那兒！ - 女士，我住在這裏
- I know I saw you there!  - Lady, I live here.
我總是經過那條隧道
I'm always in that tunnel.
但是你看見…你看見什麼了？
But what did you see?
那天晚上發生了什麼？你看見了什麼？
What happened that night? What did you see?
你摔倒在地，你跌倒了，我覺得你可憐
You busted your ass. You fell. I felt sorry for you.
我想扶你站起來，你讓我滾開
I tried to help you up. You told me to fuck off.
- 所以我就滾開了  - 我和別人在一起嗎？我一個人？
- So, I fucked off.  - Was I with anyone? Was I alone?
- 發生什麼事了？！ - 我不知道
- What happened?!  - I don't know.
你喝得大醉，你總是酩酊大醉
You were wasted. You're always wasted.
我只能告訴你這麼多了
That's all I can tell you.
喔哦，別激動
Whoa. Take it easy.
我需要你告訴我他媽的真相
I need you to tell me the fucking truth.
那晚你看見什麼了？那晚發生什麼了？
What did you see that night? What happened that night?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想一定是最糟糕的事
I'm assuming it's the worst.
天哪…
God...
過來一下，就一下
Come here for one second. Just one second.
說「操你媽，安娜 · 博伊德」
Say "Fuck you, Anna Boyd."
操你媽，安娜 · 博伊德！
Fuck you, Anna Boyd!
我很好奇她是否知道就在她寶貝…
I wonder if she knows that I fucked Tom.
當我看到那個女人在親吻另一個人時
When I saw that woman kissing someone else,
她背叛了她的丈夫，我感覺到了徹底的憤怒
betraying her husband. I felt it. Pure rage.
如何有可能，我會去她的家
If I could, I'd go to her house,
找到正坐在…
find her sitting...
把她的頭一遍一遍地砸向地面！
and I'd smash her head all over the floor!!
凱茜，感謝你為我所做的一切
Cathy, thank you for all you have done for me.
很抱歉以這樣的方式離開，過後我會找人來取我的東西
I'm sorry to leave this way. I'll send for my things later.
愛你，蕾切爾
Love, Rachel.
說的太對了，那是史上最爛的餐館
It's so true. It's the worst restaurant ever.
為什麼我們還老是回去？
Why do we keep going back?
瑪莎？
Martha?
蕾切爾？
Rachel?
有一百萬年沒見到你了…
I haven't seen you in a million years...
是啊，我本來想給你打電話，可湯姆說我還是別提這事為好
Yeah, I wanted to call you, but Tom said I should just leave it alone.
我太抱歉了
I'm so sorry.
為了什麼？
For what?
為了那天的燒烤
For the barbecue.
我只希望讓你知道我不記得任何事了，我完全失去了記憶…
I just need you to know that I don't remember anything and I just completely blacked out...
大傢伙都喝得有點兒多，所以…沒關係的
Everyone had a little too much to drink, so... It's okay.
我知道，可是用惡魔蛋…然後我衝著你吼叫
I know, but with the eggs... And then I screamed at you.
我那麼惡語傷人，我感到…我太為此感到丟人了
That I was that abusive. I just feel... I just feel so ashamed about it.
我沒有…
I don't...
湯姆…湯姆說我砸碎了你們的盤子，我不知…
Tom... Tom said that I smashed your plate. I don't...
湯姆因為我的行為被解雇了
Tom was fired because of how I behaved.
你當時感到不適，就在我家客房臥室裏小睡了一覺
You felt sick and you took a nap in our guest bedroom.
你想躺下來嗎？跟我來
Do you want to lie down? Come with me.
勞駕…蕾切爾？感覺好點了嗎？
Excuse us... Rachel? Are you feeling better?
如果願意的話，你們可以住一晚上
You guys can stay the night if you want.
不，不，沒事的，謝謝
No, no. That's fine. Thanks.
我想如果你當時大吵大鬧的話，我一定會記得的
I think I'd remember if you caused a scene.
我太抱歉了
I'm so sorry.
起來！
Get up.
然後湯姆就帶你回家了
And then Tom took you home.
- 對不起，湯姆…  - 少他媽的說這話！
- I'm sorry, Tom...  - Stop fucking saying that!
- 我知道你對不起！ - 對不起
- I know you're sorry.  - I'm sorry.
你他媽的有什麼毛病？
What's your fucking problem?
你都不能集中注意力，你他媽的站都站不穩
You can't even focus on me. You can't even fucking stand up.
你怎麼回事？你站得穩嗎？
What is wrong with you? Can you stand?
真你媽噁心！
Fucking disgusting.
不…不…
No... No...
是的，湯姆被解雇是因為他不能把自己的雞巴掖進褲襠裏
Yeah. Tom got fired because he couldn't keep his dick in his pants.
你沒做錯任何事
You did nothing wrong.
媽的，蕾切爾！快他媽的醒醒！
Fuck up, Rachel! Wake the fuck up!
醒醒！
Wake up!
你就睡在這外面吧
You can sleep out here.
我們都太為你難過了
We all felt so bad for you.
那樣一個壞蛋
Such a bad guy.
天哪
God.
你還好嗎？
Are you okay?
湯姆
貝克特
密碼不對，再試一次
湯姆
貝克特路十三號
密碼不對，再試一次
我需要見你
I need to see you.
三點鐘見我
Meet me at 3.
我到了，你在哪裏？
I'm here, where are you?
不行，照看伊維脫不開身
I can't. Stuck watching Evie.
還不睡在幹嘛？
What are you doing up?
收拾伊維的爛攤子
Picking up after Evie.
阿茲利
默西學院
你個賤貨！
You whore!
別來打攪我們
Leave us alone.
沒有新留言，沒有保存的留言
No new messages. No saved messages.
想聽你目前設置的語音郵件招呼，請按「二」
To hear your current voice-mail greeting, please press TWO.
嗨，我是梅根，留個口信
Hi, it's Megan. Leave a message.
重放這條招呼，按「一」
To replay this greeting, press ONE.
嗨，我是梅根，留個口信
Hi, it's Megan. Leave a message.
你沒事吧？
You okay?
我想我聽到了什麼動靜
I thought I heard something.
如果你聽到什麼動靜，你應該叫醒我
You should wake me up if you heard something.
我就想…
I just...
回床上去吧
Come back to bed.
賤貨！
Whore!
蕾切爾在後面
Rachel's down there.
你他媽的想幹嘛？
What the hell are you doing?
嘿，他媽的滾開！快他媽的滾！
Hey, get the fuck out of here. Get the fuck out of here!
你沒事，只是需要些幫助
You're okay. You just need some help.
別碰我，別碰我，滾開
Don't touch me. Don't touch me. Just fuck off.
滾開！
Fuck off!
- 來吧  - 安娜
- Come here.  - Anna.
- 不，不  - 安娜，別這樣，別這樣
- No, no.  - Anna, please.
走開，走！
Go away. Go.
我…我就站在這裏，我不會再靠近了
I'm just going to stand right here. I'm not gonna come closer.
我只是需要和你談談
I just need to talk to you.
我不想聽從你嘴裏說出來的任何話
I don't want to hear anything you have to say.
湯姆在哪兒？
Where's Tom?
他在騙你，他一直在欺騙，他騙術高超
He's lying to you. He always does. He's a good liar.
我知道他騙術高超
I know he's a good liar.
我們背著你往來了好幾個月
We went behind your back for months.
- 他也是這樣對你的…  - 我知道他在欺騙我
- He's just done it to you...  - I know he's cheating.
我知道
I know.
- 安娜…他殺了梅根  - 不，我們沒…我們沒證據
- Anna... He killed Megan.  - No, we don't... We don't know that.
- 他很危險  - 我們沒任何證據！
- He's dangerous.  - We don't know anything!
- 安娜，你必須離開  - 不
- Anna, you need to leave.  - No.
你必須離開，你必須把伊維帶走
You need to leave. You need to take Evie
- 你必須離開  - 不
- and you need to leave.  - No.
- 離開這裏  - 我不會離開他
- Get out of here.  - I'm not leaving him.
這又不是他第一次劈腿
It's hardly the first time he's had an affair.
這不僅僅是劈腿，你內心深處也很清楚
It's not about the affair. And you know that, deep down.
- 安娜，請跟我走吧  - 我不會離開他
- Anna, please just come with me.  - I'm not leaving him.
請跟我走
Please come with me.
- 安娜，別，別！求你了！ - 進屋裏來，親愛的
- Anna, dont. Dont! Please.  - Come in the house, honey.
我看見你了，湯姆，你個混蛋，我看見你了！你個殺人犯！
I saw you, Tom. You motherfucker, I saw you! You murderer!
你個該死的殺人犯！你殺了她！你他媽的殺了她，我知道！
You fucking murderer! You killed her! You fucking killed her, I know it!
你簡直不可他媽的理喻！
You're un-fucking-believable.
現在聽著，你聽我說，梅根那天晚上上了他的車
Now listen. Listen to me. Megan got into his car that night.
你以為我不記得了，你以為我失憶了，我見到過你
You think I don't remember. You thought I blacked out. I saw you.
梅根為什麼要上你的車？梅根上你的車了嗎？
Why did Megan get in your car? Did Megan get in your car?
- 沒有！ - 有，她上去了
- No!  - Yes, she did.
告訴她真相吧，現在就告訴她真相
Tell her the truth. Just tell her the truth right now.
你在那隧道裏攻擊了我，因為我看見她和你在一起
You attacked me in that tunnel, because I saw her with you.
我發現梅根的手機了
I found Megan's phone.
我發現了
I found it.
所以所有那些打來的電話，都不是來自蕾切爾
So, all those phone calls. They weren't from Rachel.
所以她在這裏幹活時，你就和她操上了？
So were you fucking her while she was here, working?
就在她照看我們的女兒的時候？！
While she was looking after our daughter?!
你總是顯得那麼疲倦
You were so tired all the time.
要怪就怪伊維
It's all about Evie.
沒錯
That's right.
- 湯姆，把她給我  - 沒事的
- Tom, give her to me.  - It's all right.
湯姆，把她給我，求你了，求你把她給我
Tom, give her to me. Please. Please give her to me.
- 她沒事的  - 我想她需要換尿布了
- It's gonna be fine.  - I think she needs changing.
求你了，求你讓我來抱她
Please? Please just give her to me.
放開她，你會傷到她的
Let her go. You're going to hurt her.
- 在這兒換  - 好的，我來給她換
- Change her here.  - Okay, I'll change her.
放開她，你會傷到她的
Let her go. You're gonna hurt her.
九一一，你有什麼…
911, what's your...
你有什麼緊急情況？
What's your emergency?
不，不，別動，別動
No no, stay. Stay.
你需要來一杯嗎？
Do you need a drink?
不
No.
不，你需要
Yeah, you do.
所有你說我做過的那些事
All those things that you said I did.
那些可怕的事，我一件都沒有做過
Those terrible things. I didn't do any of them.
你眼睜睜地看著我受苦，讓我覺得我是那麼一無是處
You just watched me suffer. You made me feel so worthless.
你讓我覺得每一件事都是我的錯
You made me think that everything was my fault.
喝吧
Drink it.
你告訴我是我讓你丟了工作
You told me I got you fired.
但是我沒有
But, I didn't.
你知道嗎，我在火車上遇見了瑪莎
You know, I saw Martha on the train.
喝啊！
Drink it!
我在火車上遇見了瑪莎，她告訴我說你被解雇…
I saw Martha on the train. And she told me that you were fired
…是因為你和辦公室裏的每一個人鬼混！
because you were fucking everyone in the office!
蕾切爾在後面
Rachel's down there.
在這兒等著
Wait here.
快到車裏來
You want to get in the car?
怎麼回事？
What's going on?
別擔心
Don't worry about it.
快點
Come on.
好了，我來了，什麼事？
Okay, I'm here. What is it?
我想到林子裏去
I just want to go to the woods.
你們女的怎麼都這麼瘋？
What is it with you crazy women?
你想要這個？
Is this what you want?
不
No.
這樣？
Like this?
- 怎麼了？ - 我懷孕了
- What?  - I'm pregnant.
恭喜了
Congratulations.
我以為你該知道
I thought you should know.
你以為我該知道？
You thought I should know?
- 有可能是你的  - 那就去做掉
- There's a chance it could be yours.  - Then get an abortion.
如果是斯科特的，隨你怎麼辦，但…
Or if it's Scott's, do whatever you want.
但如果不是，那就…把它打掉
But if it's not then... Get rid of it.
你本可以更加積極一點
You can be as involved as you want.
你是個爛保姆
You're a shitty nanny.
什麼讓你覺得你會成為一個好母親？
What makes you think you're gonna be a good mother?
當初你為什麼要帶我去你家？
Why did you bring me there in the first place?
因為我認為那會很有趣，有你們兩個人在那兒
Because I thought it would be fun to have you both around.
我按你的遊戲來玩，好讓你在伊維的…
I played your game so you could fuck me
家長們安排的帶著孩子們一起玩的聚會
- …玩伴聚會之間干我  - 我不需要再有個孩子
- in between Evie's playdates.  - I don't need another kid.
肯定不要和你的
Certainly not with you.
我為了接近你甚至去照顧你的小孩！
I took care of your kid to be near you!
你干了安娜，因為你再也幹不了蕾切爾！
You fucked Anna because you couldn't fuck Rachel anymore!
你干了我，因為你再也幹不了安娜！
And you fucked me because you couldn't fuck Anna!
干了我們所有人，可你不過是個可悲的、性無能的衰人！
Take us all away and you're just a pathetic, impotent man!
你不可能擺脫掉我
You're not gonna get rid of me.
你這一輩子都將為這個孩子付出代價
You're gonna pay for this child for the rest of your life.
你像條狗
You're like a dog.
像一條沒人要的、受盡虐待的狗
Like one of those unwanted, mistreated dogs.
你可以踹它們，可它們還是一直回來找你
You can kick them, but they keep coming back to you.
以為要是自己怎麼著乖一點…
Thinking that somehow if they're good...
你不能再這樣對待我
You're not doing this again.
…你就會愛它們
You'll love them.
你就是這麼做的，你不能再這樣對待我
This is what you do. You're not doing this to me.
這都是你自找的，蕾切爾
You brought this on yourself, Rachel.
如果那一個晚上你躲得遠遠的…
If you had just stayed away that one night...
沒過來找我們麻煩
Just left us all alone.
梅根也是你害的
You brought this on Megan.
某種意義上說，你殺了她
In a way, you killed her.
但我沒殺
But I didn't.
你殺的
You did.
你殺了我們婚姻中的我
You did this to me in our marriage.
你讓我快他媽的發瘋了
You made me fucking crazy.
你知不知道和一個滿腦子糨糊的人結婚是什麼樣的感覺？
Do you have any idea what it's like to be married to a fucking blur?
我沒別的選擇，他…
I had no choice. He was...
他會殺了我的
He would have killed me.
我也不想傷害他
I never wanted to hurt him.
這是正當防衛
It was self-defense.
她沒別的選擇
She had no choice.
湯姆會殺了她的
Tom would have killed her.
整個過程我都看見了
I saw the whole thing.
蕾切爾說梅根的事是對的
Rachel was right about Megan.
她說的所有事都是對的
She was right about everything.
梅根 · 希普韋爾
1990 — 2016
現在我們永遠扯平了，我們三個人
We are tied forever now, the three of us.
被我們共同的故事永遠綁在了一起
Bound forever by the story we share.
今天，我坐在另一節車廂裏，我抬頭看向前方
Today, I sit in a different car. And I look ahead.
一切皆有可能
Anything is possible.
因為我不再是從前的那個女孩
Because I am not the girl I used to be.